var question1 = {
    question: "What is the name of Rudolph's dad?",
    option1: "Vixon",
    option2: "Dixon",
    option3: "Dasher",
    option4: "Donner",
    answer: 4 //Donner
};

var question2 = {
    question: 'Who wrote "The Nightmare Before Christmas"?',
    option1: 'Alfred Hitchcock',
    option2: 'Martin Scorsese',
    option3: 'Steven Speilberg',
    option4: 'Tim Burton',
    answer: 4 //Tim Burton
};

var question3 = {
    question: 'The rabbit in the magic hat in "Frosty the Snowman" is named:',
    option1: 'Scut Farkus',
    option2: 'Little Grinch',
    option3: 'Hocus Pocus',
    option4: 'Rabbit Claus',
    answer: 3 //Hocus Pocus
    
};

var question4 = {
    question: 'Who is the guardian angel of George Bailey named in "It\'s a Wonderful Life"?',
    option1: 'Lewis',
    option2: 'Clarence',
    option3: 'Robert',
    option4: 'lawrence',
    answer: 2 //Clarence
};

var question5 = {
    question: 'What did Ralphie want for Christmas in "A Christmas Story"?',
    option1: 'A Remote Controlled Car',
    option2: 'A BB Gun',
    option3: 'A Bow and Arrow',
    option4: 'A Red Wagon',
    answer: 2 //A BB Gun
};

var question6 = {
    question: "What is the Scrooge's first name?",
    option1: 'Hezekiah',
    option2: 'Ebenezer',
    option3: 'Maxwell',
    option4: 'Martin',
    answer: 2 //Ebenezer
};

var question7 = {
    question: "Why was the Grinch so nasty? Because he had a:",
    option1: 'Broken Heart',
    option2: 'Small Brain',
    option3: 'Small Heart',
    option4: 'Sore Back',
    answer: 3 //Small Heart
};

var question8 = {
    question: "What city did 'Miracle on 34th Street' take place in?",
    option1: "Chicago",
    option2: "San Fransisco",
    option3: "New York",
    option4: "Boston",
    answer: 3 //New York
};

var question9 = {
    question: "What did Clarence get for accomplishing his mission in \"It's a Wonderful Life\"?",
    option1: "A Trumpet",
    option2: "Wings",
    option3: "A Halo",
    option4: "A Feather",
    answer: 2 //Wings
};

var question10 = {
    question: "Two men broke into a house during Christmas and had a LOT of trouble in which movie?",
    option1: "101 Dalmatians",
    option2: "Christmas Trouble",
    option3: "Home Alone",
    option4: "The Santa Clause",
    answer: 3 //Home Alone
    
};
